<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>a philanthropy project to enable all children to flourish on Threshing Floor Foundation</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in a philanthropy project to enable all children to flourish on Threshing Floor Foundation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Genesis of the project</title>
      <link>/posts/genesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/genesis/</guid>
      <description>Introductory post Introductory post on why we wanted to start this philanthropy project&#xA;Internal goals of (i) giving back, (ii) gaining experience in running philanthropy with personal capital before been entrusted with external funding, (iii) to practice donating money effectively, (iv) to learn how money can best be used to help those in need, (v) matching funds to increase dollar impact, (vi) to learn about the conditions of the world outside of Australia/New Zealand…</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why &#39;Threshing Floor&#39;?</title>
      <link>/posts/name/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/name/</guid>
      <description>test sustenance, care, protection, provision, transformation &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>draft We want to figure out how best to support children in orphanages. Which orphanages actually require funding? Are orpahanages necessary, is there a better solution? How can we generate sustainable funding? So we&amp;rsquo;re going to start small, experiment, figure out the optimal solutions, and then scale up so that all children have an opportunity to flourish.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll document everything here.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
